aboutthedata.com 2018-04-23

# AboutTheData.com | Privacy

## Privacy Policy for this Website ([www.AboutTheData.com](http://www.aboutthedata.com/ "www.aboutthedata.com"))

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Acxiom Corporation on [www.AboutTheData.com](http://www.aboutthedata.com/ "www.aboutthedata.com") and is designed to ensure that visitors to this website understand how and why Acxiom collects and uses information provided by users of this site.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

#### Use by Acxiom Corporation

This website allows you to view, edit and remove information about you in Acxiom’s marketing data products and allows you to view information about you from our 3rd party marketing partners that we make available for digital advertising and to learn about Acxiom’s digital marketing data products and services. The information you provide during registration, such as your name, address and email address, along with edits made to elements, may be included in Acxiom’s marketing to you, Acxiom’s marketing data products and shared with our partners. This will enable our clients and partners to deliver more relevant marketing and advertising to you. 

To access data about you, you are required to provide personally identifiable information, so Acxiom can verify your identity. The information you provide will also be used to support your relationship with Acxiom on this website, including making the site easier for you to use and informing you of services, products or site updates, new services or products and other related information from Acxiom.

To fulfill a particular request, the information you provide may be shared within the Acxiom Corporation family of businesses. 

#### Use by Third Parties

The information you provide during registration, such as your name, address and email address, along with edits and removals made to elements, may be reflected in Acxiom’s marketing data products which are used by Acxiom and our clients. Acxiom provides marketing data products to our clients, partners and qualified businesses, non-profit organizations and other entities to enable them to deliver more relevant marketing and advertising to you. The resulting marketing offers and advertising you may receive may be via the mail, email, telephone and, if you opted in, on your mobile phone. To learn more about any of these uses and the privacy policy associated with them, [here](http://acxiom.com/about-acxiom/privacy/).

Acxiom may share aggregated information, such as the number of visitors to the site, with our partners and third parties to develop suggestions to improve our website accessibility and the services provided on the site. Aggregated data is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Acxiom may use contractors and other service providers to help us deliver content and fulfill requests made on this site. However, in these instances, the information you provide remains the property of Acxiom Corporation.

In addition, we reserve the right to disclose the information you provided as required by law and when we believe disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website.

This website may also contain links to other sites not owned by Acxiom. Please be aware that Acxiom is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you, when you leave this site, to read the privacy statements of these other sites.

#### Technologies

Acxiom uses technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are visited most often and understand traffic patterns on pages.

Cookies: This site uses cookies to tailor web content to match your browser capability. You can set your Internet browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. If you reject the cookie, you may still use this site, but you may be limited in the functionality of some areas. For more information about cookies, visit [How Cookies Work](http://www.acxiom.com/About-Acxiom/Privacy/How-Cookies-Work/).

Sensors: To determine your ability to receive HTML-based e-mail messages, Acxiom may include a coded sensor in its HTML-based e-mail messages. The sensor activates when the e-mail message is opened and flags the e-mail address of the recipient as one that is capable of receiving HTML-based e-mail messages. This capability helps us to send the e-mail in a format you can read, which allows us to track the aggregate number of e-mails read and to measure, in aggregate, if any of the links in the e-mail were accessed. No other information is collected or used. If the recipient cannot receive HTML e-mails, the recipient will not receive a functioning sensor.

Log Files: We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ activities and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in improving the site. 

Do Not Track Signals: This website does not recognize browser “do-not-track” signals or similar mechanisms. 

### YOUR CHOICES AND HOW TO CONTACT US

Acxiom also gives consumers the opportunity to learn about all of our data products at our corporate website [www.acxiom.com](http://www.acxiom.com/). Consumers who wish to opt-out of all Acxiom marketing data products, and Acxiom's use of third party data products we offer, may complete and submit an opt-out request form by clicking [here](https://isapps.acxiom.com/optout/optout.aspx). To opt out of just our online cookie based advertising products, click [here](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/). Access to information about you in our directory and our fraud detection and prevention products is provided in the form of a US Reference Information Report that is available for a processing fee of $5. You may complete and submit a request form for your US Reference Information Report by clicking [here](http://acxiom.com/about-acxiom/privacy/us-reference-info-report/). 

You may opt-out of receiving email marketing from us by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in the email.

#### Questions

If you have any questions about Acxiom’s www.AboutTheData.com website functionality or the www.AboutTheData.com privacy policy, e-mail us at [support@aboutthedata.com](mailto:support@aboutthedata.com). 

### SECURITY INFORMATION

Acxiom takes security seriously. We maintain security procedures designed to ensure information we own, license and process is not accessed by any unauthorized person or business. We use a variety of multi-level security systems to control access to our services and information products. Acxiom associates and all users at client locations must have access codes and the authorization to access certain data and applications.

We also regularly conduct risk assessments and audits on our internal and external information systems. These security measures help us continually assess our ability to maintain the security of our data. Our enterprise network security operations center maintains real-time monitoring for information system vulnerabilities and unauthorized access attempts into Acxiom’s systems. We also maintain strict physical security for our facilities and limit access to critical areas of our business.

#### Notification of Changes

This policy was last revised in June 2015. Our methods of information collection and uses of the information are unchanged.

If we decide to change our privacy policy in a material way, we will post a notification highlighting those changes on our home page.

If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify affected individuals by email if the consumer has provided an email address to us and by posting a notice on this website. Individuals can choose whether or not to allow Acxiom to use information about them in this new manner. If we do not receive permission, we will use the information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

In the event Acxiom is purchased, data collected on this site will be one of the transferred assets.

Effective Date: June 19, 2015
